[roars]
Strange beasts
and monsters.
Vast riches.
Hidden treasures.
Evil haunts.
Uncharted frontiers.
The mysterious unknown.
The people who are captivated by the magic
in those words...
are called...
Hunters.
[theme song playing]
[gasps]
Sorry, I was careless
and he got away.
[Hisoka] Don't lie to me.
He probably begged you to grant him
a last request
and you relented.
Am I right?
[Gitarrackur]
Well, I may have felt sorry for the man.
He was going to die anyway.
You really need to stop pitying those
who serve no purpose.
I do have standards.
Why waste time on people
who are utterly useless.
I only spare those
whose premature deaths would be a waste.
DEFEAT x AND x DISGRACE
[narrator]
Hisoka targets Kurapika and Leorio
as Gon goes after Hisoka's badge.
Under the dark silent cover of night,
something is about to happen.
[crickets chirping]
Now, run!
[cries out]
Yes, I remember them.
This should be fun.
[Gon]
It looks like Hisoka's found his prey.
[grunts]
Leorio, Kurapika.
I never thought he'd be going after
Leorio and Kurapika.
What am I supposed to do now?
Don't lose focus. Stick to the plan!
And the moment Hisoka attacks,
go for his badge.
That's the best chance
I'm going to get to take it.
It's my only chance.
[panting]
No, I can't.
if they start fighting,
I'll have to change my strategy.
[Leorio] All right, so,
I finally figured out who my target is.
But how am I supposed to find her
on an island this big?
Isn't wandering around like this
a huge waste of energy?
No more a waste of energy
than constantly whining, I would imagine.
Well you've already got your six points
so you're all set.
But I'm plumb out of luck
if I don't find my target pretty soon.
[both grunt]
Hey.
Hisoka.
What a coincidence meeting you here.
How fortunate.
[laughs] Why do I run into people
I don't want to see?
You see, all I'm lacking
is just two more points.
I was hoping you might give me yours.
Give you what?
You're crazy. I'm not going to give--
Leorio.
You said you only need two points.
Meaning neither one of us
is your primary target.
Am I right about that?
Leave the questions to me, all right?
Will you give me your badges?
Answer carefully.
I suppose that depends...
Between the two of us
we currently have four badges.
Mine, my target's, Leorio's,
and one that's worth only a single point
to either him or me.
Of the four, two might possibly belong
to your specific target,
and only two.
Mine or the badge
that's worth a single point.
Leorio's number is 403.
He was targeted by number 16,
Tonpa.
And he,
number 16, was assigned to me
as my target.
Each of us was given a different target
so 16 and 403 are out.
[Hisoka] Indeed.
Neither of those is the target
I was searching for.
What of it?
[Kurapika]
That just leaves the other two badges.
If you're willing to take the badge
that's worth one point and leave
you are more than welcome to have it.
But I will not allow you to take mine.
And the same goes for the other two.
If you insist on taking them by force
prepare to fight me for them.
[chuckles]
-[Hisoka laughs]
-[Kurapika and Leorio gasp]
[purrs]
Out of curiosity, what is your number?
Four hundred and four.
[Hisoka] Very well.
You have yourself a deal.
I'll take the badge worth a single point.
[gasps]
I'll leave it here.
Don't look so concerned.
I'll stay right here
until you're out of sight.
[laughs]
In a few short days,
they've both grown beyond recognition.
But, they have more to learn.
I wonder...
why must unripe fruit be so...
tantalizing.
Such a pity.
Not the badge I was hoping for.
[exhales with relief]
[Gon]
That was a close one.
But now,
I've only got one more chance left.
Whenever he finds his next prey,
I'll be ready.
Hey.
Wait just a minute.
What if the next person he finds decides
that they don't want to fight him either?
Oh man.
If the next person just surrenders
and hands over their badge,
like what I just saw happen,
I won't get another chance at all.
I'm so stupid!
Geez, why didn't I think of that?
[groans]
[Hisoka sighs]
[gasps]
[birds cawing]
[wind blowing]
[squeaking]
[whimpers]
I'm so scared.
I don't want to be here anymore.
I feel his bloodlust.
[groans] Oh no...
They had to go
and get me stirred up,
there's only one thing to do about it now.
I have to quell it.
[moans]
[birds chirping]
[waves crashing gently]
[whimpers softly]
[Hisoka] Well.
Time to go.
I can do this.
His bloodlust is gone.
but that look in his eyes
is nothing like before.
He's going to attack the next person
he sees,
even if they try to surrender,
I'm sure of it.
I know, I've got to move ahead
and find his next prey before he does.
Then, I need to find myself
a good spot to hide
and wait for my chance.
There!
I've only got about a minute or so
before Hisoka spots it.
I need to figure out where
their paths are going to cross.
Got it!
Gotta hurry.
[grunts]
Hisoka will attack
the second he notices that guy.
If I want to steal his badge,
this is it.
It's the last chance I'm going to get.
HUNTER GLOSSARY
CHANCE
[waves crashing gently]
[footsteps]
[Gon] It feels like Hisoka has
completely hidden his presence.
He's going to find me.
I just know it!
[panting]
I'll have to conceal my presence too.
[footsteps]
[footsteps audible]
[complete silence]
[Gon] I have to stay hidden.
I can't let him sense me.
Focus.
Hmm?
[rumbling]
Here he comes.
[grunts]
[man] Hisoka!
Damn it. Bring it on!
[Gon] He's fighting back.
[whimpering]
[cries out]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[panting]
[Gon continues panting]
I did it. I took Hisoka's badge from him.
[groans]
[grunts]
[footsteps approaching]
[man] About 7,000.
Do you know what that number represents?
That is the number of chances I had
to kill you.
But it's also
about the number of times you cast
your fishing rod while you were training.
Every cast left you wide open,
but your focus and your accuracy
were admirable, I'll give you that.
And just now, your swing was
equally impressive.
But you didn't pay enough attention
to your surroundings.
In the future,
remember to watch your back.
So long.
[Gon] Damn it.
[strained breathing]
[rustling]
[Gon gasps]
You surprise me.
You hid your presence from me while you
were waiting for your chance to strike.
Biding your time until the very moment
that I attacked someone else?
Did you learn how to conceal yourself
all on your own?
Marvelous.
You're like a wild animal.
And your timing was just impeccable.
You were able to conceal
your bloodlust
by cleverly hiding it behind mine
so that I wouldn't notice.
Masterfully done.
His blow dart delivered a fast-acting,
powerful muscle relaxant.
In a normal person
the effect lasts about ten days.
There are three days left.
I'm sure by then
you'll make a full recovery.
[Gon straining] Wait.
If you're not taking your badge
then why are you here?
To say, "Congratulations."
As it turns out, he was my target.
Which means I don't need mine anymore.
Well, neither do I.
[Hisoka] Don't be like that.
You owe me one now.
You can pay me back
whenever you like.
So long.
[Gon straining]
I don't owe you or anybody.
Here, take it back.
[laughs]
I refuse.
I've decided to let you live, for now.
And I plan to let you continue living
for as long as it suits me.
Until some day,
you become truly worthy of killing.
I will take it back,
but only when you can punch me
in the face like that.
In the meantime,
you just hold onto it for me.
[Hisoka laughs]
[narrator]
Gon was knocked out by Hisoka's punch
and realized he was utterly helpless
in the face of such power.
And now, alone in the darkness,
what must be going through his mind?
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Next time:
"Trap x in x the Hole."
Holy moly.
-I want to be your friend.
-Wow. Friend?
You're embarrassing.